Where will your dreams take you?
Sing 2 is a family, comedy, music film directed by Garth Jennings.
Buster and his new cast now have their sights set on debuting a new show
at the Crystal Tower Theater in glamorous Redshore City.
But with no connections, he and his singers must sneak into the Crystal Entertainment offices, run by the ruthless wolf mogul Jimmy
Crystal, where the gang pitches the ridiculous idea of casting the lion rock legend Clay Calloway in their show.
Buster must embark on a quest to find the now-isolated Clay
and persuade him to return to the stage.
Buster Moon (voice), played by Matthew McConaughey.
Rosita (voice), played by Reese Witherspoon.
Ash (voice), played by Scarlett Johansson.
Johnny (voice), played by Taron Egerton.
Mr. Crystal (voice), played by Bobby Cannavale.
Meena (voice), played by Tori Kelly.
Sing 2 is a 2021 American animated jukebox musical comedy
film written and directed by Garth Jennings.
Matthew McConaughey, Reese Witherspoon, Scarlett Johansson, Taron Egerton, Tori Kelly, Nick Kroll, and Nick Offerman reprise their roles from the
first film, with Bobby Cannavale, Halsey, Pharrell Williams, Letitia Wright, Eric André, Chelsea Peretti, and Bono joining the cast.
The plot involves Buster Moon and his group putting on a show in Redshore City while working to
impress an entertainment mogul and enlist a reclusive rock star to perform with the group.
Sing 2 had its world premiere at the AFI Fest on November 14, 2021, and was
theatrically released in the United States on December 22 by Universal Pictures.
The film received mixed reviews from critics and grossed $408 million against a budget of $85 million,
becoming the highest-grossing animated film of 2021 and the tenth-highest-grossing film of 2021.
A further sequel is in development.
The film explores themes of wolf, stage, villain, sequel, anthropomorphism.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.